Independence Historical Society records, Inclusive: 1836-2020, undated, Bulk: 1965-1994
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Literary Productions, 1899-2011, undated; 4
  - Clippings: Washington County, 1969 October-1970 March 11 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Clippings: Washington County, 1970 March 12-November 24 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Clippings: Washington County, 1970 November 25-1971 March (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Clippings: Washington County, 1971 April-1989 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Clippings: Washington County (1 of 4), undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Clippings: Washington County (2 of 4), undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Clippings: Washington County (3 of 4), undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Clippings: Washington County (4 of 4), undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Photographic Materials and Media, 1945-1984; 5
  General condition: Good.
  This series contains photographs of historic properties around Independence, plus other pictures pertaining to the Independence Historical Society and historic preservation in Washington County. All original photographs were copied during processing, with only the copies filed due to extensive damage to the originals. The one exception to this is the original Baylor Centennial photograph, which was kept.
  - Photographs: General, 1969, undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Photographs: Baylor Centennial, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Photographs: Historical Marker Dedication, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Photographs: Asbury-Daniels House (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Photographs: Asbury-Daniels House (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Photographs: Independence Baptist Church, 1967, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Photographs: Seward Plantation, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - The Legacy of John P. Coles, undated (Box 6, Folder 43)